{
    "subject": "resource/Slowdive",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Shoegazing",
    "human_readable": "Slowdive's genre is Shoegazing.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8959881067276001,
            "question": "Besides Slowdive, which other bands are considered Shoegazers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6600274443626404,
            "question": "What genre of music is Slowdive known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5830638408660889,
            "question": "Can you name a musical genre associated with Slowdive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5569503307342529,
            "question": "To what musical style does Slowdive belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4860146939754486,
            "question": "Slowdive's music falls under which category?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47420480847358704,
            "question": "What kind of music does the band Slowdive play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46593376994132996,
            "question": "Give an example of a band known for the Shoegazing genre."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37652039527893066,
            "question": "What is the defining characteristic of Shoegazing music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3578253388404846,
            "question": "What are some key elements of Shoegazing music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28579580783843994,
            "question": "How would you describe the overall sound of Shoegaze music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Slowdive's genre is Shoegazing.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4621_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key elements of Shoegazing music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4621_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the defining characteristic of Shoegazing music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4621_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Give an example of a band known for the Shoegazing genre.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4621_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4621_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Slowdive is a British band associated with the shoegaze genre, and that they have been referred to as one of the best acts out there right now due to their unique sound and style, which is characteristic of shoegazing music."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly indicate that Slowdive is associated with the shoegaze genre, and provide details about their music and influence within this genre."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}